Governor's Efficiency Study Commission SR.397
State Archives of North Carolina
- Working Files, SR.397.3; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
  - Universities, 19; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
    - University of North Carolina at Greensboro: Individual Recommendation Reports, 1973; 4117; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Greensboro: Individual Recommendation Reports)
    - University of North Carolina at Greensboro: Self-Study (folder 1 of 3), 1972; 4118; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Greensboro: Self-Study (folder 1 of 3))
    - University of North Carolina at Greensboro: Self-Study (folder 2 of 3), 1972; 4119; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Greensboro: Self-Study (folder 2 of 3))
    - University of North Carolina at Greensboro: Self-Study (folder 3 of 3), 1972; 4120; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Greensboro: Self-Study (folder 3 of 3))
    - University of North Carolina System: Budget Requests (folder 1 of 3), 1973-1975; 4121; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina System: Budget Requests (folder 1 of 3))
    - University of North Carolina System: Budget Requests (folder 2 of 3), 1973-1975; 4122; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina System: Budget Requests (folder 2 of 3))
    - University of North Carolina System: Budget Requests (folder 3 of 3), 1973-1975; 4123; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina System: Budget Requests (folder 3 of 3))
    - University of North Carolina System: Computer Recommendations, 1973; 4124; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina System: Computer Recommendations)
    - University of North Carolina System: Development and Equipment Acquisition, 1973; 4125; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina System: Development and Equipment Acquisition)
    - University of North Carolina System: General Warehouse and Stores, 1972; 4126; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina System: General Warehouse and Stores)
    - University of North Carolina System: Implementation Progress Report, 1973-1975; 4127; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina System: Implementation Progress Report)
    - University of North Carolina System Recommendations: In Process, 1973-1975; 4128; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina System Recommendations: In Process)
    - University of North Carolina System Recommendations: More Study, 1973-1975; 4129; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina System Recommendations: More Study)
    - University of North Carolina System Recommendations: Unacceptable, 1973; 4130; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina System Recommendations: Unacceptable)
    - University of North Carolina at Wilmington, 1971-1973; 4131; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Wilmington)
    - University of North Carolina at Wilmington: Publications (folder 1 of 2), 1971-1973; 4132; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Wilmington: Publications (folder 1 of 2))
    - University of North Carolina at Wilmington: Publications (folder 2 of 2), 1971-1973; 4133; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Wilmington: Publications (folder 2 of 2))
    - University of North Carolina at Wilmington: Self-Study, 1971; 4134; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Wilmington: Self-Study)
    - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education, 1972; 4135; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education)
    - Western Carolina University, 1973; 4136; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Western Carolina University)
    - Winston-Salem State University, 1971-1973; 4137; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Winston-Salem State University)